[Music]
wow
[Applause]
fwd
under a pale blue sky
you never felt so cold
another sleepless night
[Music]
never know we
can
go there
[Music]
uh
headed for the open doors
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
never going
so they're gonna know
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
um
foreign
[Applause]
china
[Music]
m
yo
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
you
foreign
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
some
[Applause]
[Music]
um
oh
[Applause]
same thing
[Laughter]
[Music]
good evening fwd cambodia it's such a
joy to see you all and i trust you are
keeping safe and staying well
i'm very thrilled to celebrate with you
this big day of after beauty cambodia
grand launch
and embark on a new chapter of the fwd
journey together
welcome to the big fwd family
and may our journey of celebrate living
begin
in december 2020
we successfully acquire bangkok life
assurance cambodia publicly visited
and started our journey to cambodia
this was an especially rewarding
achievement in these very extraordinary
times
entering our tenth market in asia has
been another remarkable milestone and
underlines our commitment to becoming a
leading pan-asian insurer
gambola cambodia has quickly evolved
into one of the southeast asia's most
vibrant and dynamic economies
we are very excited to see how its
insurance market is developing and the
tremendous potential of the country
as a trailblazer we challenge the
traditional practices and hope to bring
fresh experience and product
propositions to our customers in the
country
that's why we are here to tell a
different insurance story and change the
way cambodian people feel about
insurance
with rothha's leadership and his
talented team i have full confidence
that we build our brand and business in
this compelling market
and play a key role in transforming the
industry
welcome again
to the fwd family and congratulations on
this successful launch
i look forward to being able to travel
to cambodia soon
and to meeting all of you in person
so for now enjoy the evening and thank
you so much
thank you mr phone
channel
i'm not going young
hello and good evening fwd cambodia i
would like to wish a very warm welcome
to everyone joining us here today at our
virtual grand launch event i'm sure this
very special day will just be the
beginning of great things to come though
of course i'm really disappointed that
we still cannot meet in person
i'm delighted to celebrate with you all
at our official launch yet another
significant milestone in our journey to
become a leading pan-asian insurer that
is changing the way people feel about
insurance
kudos to each and every one of you for
your hard work and dedication in making
this launch such a success especially
during this difficult time amid the
pandemic
it was definitely not an easy journey in
the face of both local
and global uncertainty but i'm so proud
at how we've been able to remain
resilient both as individuals and as a
business
the move into cambodia is an exciting
milestone for our southeast asian
ambitions
in this rapidly growing economy still
with relatively low insurance
penetration we see enormous
opportunities to provide financial
security to the people of cambodia as we
strive to expand our presence across the
region
i'm confident that we can all make great
progress and create long-term success in
cambodia through offering a different
kind of insurance experience through our
products and services
once again
congratulations on the successful launch
tonight
i'm pleased to begin this exciting new
chapter with you all and really look
forward to working together to continue
bringing fresh and positive insurance
experiences to our staff to our
distribution partners and of course to
our customers
i wish you all a most enjoyable evening
have a great night
take care and
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
in
[Music]
i
is
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
i don't care what you say
i say hey
i'll do it for myself
put all the bad things away
hey
[Music]
away
[Applause]
[Music]
eh
do i
do it
for you
[Music]
retry suspended